gminsights.com 2018-07-21

# Global Market Insights - Privacy Policy, Information Security, Contact Details for Visitors / Customers and Policy Updates

**1.             _INTRODUCTION_**  

1.1.        Global Market Insights, Inc. (the “ **Company** ”) is an entity registered in Selbyville, Delaware engaged in the business of conducting market research and providing management consulting to entities across the globe (the “ **Services** ”). The Company is committed to ensuring that privacy of its clients, visitors, and other users of the Company Website <https://www.gminsights.com/> (the “ **Website** ”) is always respected. This Website Privacy Policy is to serve as a testament to our sincere efforts to uphold privacy laws.  

1.2.         The protection and security of your Personal Information and Usage Information ( _as defined below_ ) is one of our top priorities. This Privacy Policy discloses and explains how we collect, use, share and protect Personal Information, Usage Information or any other information about you. We also provide information regarding how you can access and update your Personal Information and make certain choices about how your Personal Information is used by us.  

1.3.         This Privacy Policy explains what information of yours will be collected by the Company when you access the Website, how the information will be used, and how you can control the collection, correction and/or deletion of information. We will not use or share your information with anyone except as described in this Privacy Policy. This Privacy Policy does not apply to information we collect by other means (including offline) or from other sources. The use of information collected through our Sites shall be limited to the purposes under this Privacy Policy and our Terms of Use to customers.  

1.4.         “ **The Company** ”, “ **We** ”, or “ **us** ” refers to Global Market Insights, Inc. and “ **you** ” refers to a user who has provided any information including Personal Information pursuant to access to the Website and using any features therein.

**2.             _INFORMATION COLLECTION BY GLOBAL MARKET INSIGHTS_**  

2.1.         **Data Controller and Data Processor:**

In accordance with the European Union General Data Protection Regulation (Regulation 2016/679), the Company controls, collects, owns and directs the use of the Personal Information and Usage Information and in this regard, the Company is the data controller and data processor. The Company is registered company in the Selbyville, Delaware with its registered office at - Global Market Insights, Inc., 4 North Main Street, Selbyville, Delaware 19975 USA. For any queries regarding this Privacy Policy and the collection and use of data collected or processed under this Privacy Policy, the Company can be contacted by mail at - Global Market Insights, Inc., Post Office Box 1027, Selbyville, Delaware 19975-1027 USA; by phone at +1-302-846-7766 or by e-mail at [legal@gminsights.com](mailto:legal@gminsights.com).  

2.2.         **Legal basis for collection and processing of Personal/Usage Information:**

The legal basis for collection and processing of any information collected and processed by the Company including the Personal Information is (i) performance of the Services in accordance with the Terms of Use; (ii) where it is in our legitimate interests to do so and not overridden by your rights (for example, in some cases for direct marketing, fraud prevention, network and information systems security, responding to your communications, the operation of networks of groups by the network administrators, and improving our Website). In some cases, we may also have a legal obligation to collect information about you, or may otherwise need the information to protect your vital interests or those of another person. We may also process information to comply with a legal requirement or to perform a contract.  

2.3.         **Basic Information**

The Company may ask you to provide the Company with certain categories of information such as personal information, which is information that could reasonably be used to identify you personally, such as your name, e-mail address, and mobile number (“ **Personal Information** ”). We may collect this information through various forms and in various places through the Website, including when you first register with us, when you create a transaction, when you contact us, when you update your information or from time to time or when you otherwise interact with us. The Company may include registration, surveys, and other online forms where users will need to provide Personal Information.  

2.4.         **Additional Information**

2.4.1      **Cookies** : The Company may use standard “cookie” browser application feature to collect and understand website usability trends. Cookies are text files that we may place in your computer browser to store your preferences.  Cookies are used to record various aspects of your visit and assist us in providing you with uninterrupted service. One of the primary purposes of cookies is to store your preferences and other information on your computer in order to save you time by eliminating the need to repeatedly enter the same information and to display your personalized content. However, no personal information identifying the user is collected nor any data capture mechanisms is employed. The user may change browser settings to accept or reject cookies on personal preference. You have the ability to accept or decline cookies. Most Web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify the browser setting to decline cookies if you so prefer. If you choose to decline cookies, you may not be able to sign in or use other interactive features of the Website that may depend on cookies. If you choose to accept cookies, you also have the ability to later delete cookies that you have accepted. If you choose to delete cookies, any settings and preferences controlled by those cookies, including advertising preferences, will be deleted and may need to be recreated. We process and keep all data for our own use  and, if you wish to opt-out from tracking by the Company you can request so by sending an email to [legal@gminsights.com](mailto:legal@gminsights.com) **.**  

2.4.2      **Information Collected Automatically** : In addition to any Personal Information or other information that you choose to submit to us, we may use a variety of technologies that automatically (or passively) collect certain information whenever you access the Website (“ **Usage Information** ”). This Usage Information may include the browser that you are using, the URL that referred you to our Website, among other information. Usage Information may be non-identifying or may be associated with you. Whenever we associate Usage Information or a Device Identifier with your Personal Information, we will treat it as Personal Information and the conditions relating to Personal Information under this Privacy Policy will be followed. Traffic data, while anonymous, is gathered and analysed for business needs.  

2.4.3      **Information Third Parties Provide About You:** We may, from time to time, supplement the information we collect about you through our Website with outside records from third parties obtained rightfully in order to enhance our ability to serve you, to tailor our content to you and to offer you opportunities to use such of our Services that we believe may be of interest to you. We may combine the information we receive from such third party sources with information we collect through the Website or through independent research conducted by the Company, with your consent. In these cases, we will apply this Privacy Policy to any Personal Information received, unless otherwise provided. We may process such information received from third parties for the legitimate commercial purposes or to enter into contractual obligations with you or to fulfil certain contractual obligations or where you have requested third parties to provide information about yourself to us.  

2.5.         **Processing of Data:**

The Company may also process any Personal Information or Usage Information collected from you for legitimate commercial purposes including providing Services. The Company implements appropriate technical and organisational measures to ensure a level of security appropriate to the risk of our processing of information about individuals such as (i) only sharing and providing access to your information to the minimum extent necessary, subject to confidentiality restrictions where appropriate, and on an anonymised basis wherever possible; (ii) using secure servers to store your information; (iii) verifying the identity of any individual who requests access to information prior to granting them access to information; and (iv) using Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) software or other similar encryption technologies to encrypt any payment transactions you make on or via our website.  

2.6.         **Right of a user in relation to data submitted** : 

Any user who has submitted Personal Information on the Website and has the right to (i)  access, correct, delete such Personal Information subject to the Company successfully verifying your identity; (ii) object to the Company processing your Personal Information on legitimate grounds; (iii) to withdraw your consent to our use of your information at any time where we rely on your consent to use or process that information; (iv) opting out of receiving any promotional or marketing material by clicking on the “Unsubscribe” button or by sending an email to [legal@gminsights.com](mailto:legal@gminsights.com). Please note that if you withdraw your consent, this will not affect the lawfulness of our use and processing of your information on the basis of your consent before the point in time when you withdraw your consent; (iv) right to have the Personal Information transferred to another data controller; and (v) lodge a complaint with a supervisory authority, in particular in the Member State of your habitual residence, place of work or of an alleged infringement of the General Data Protection Regulation. Any request received by the Company by the user in relation to the aforesaid shall be acknowledged by the Company within seventy-two (72) business hours.  

**3.             _USE OF INFORMATION COLLECTED_**  

3.1.         **_Business Purposes:_**

The Company does not share any Personal Information with any third party without your consent, except when directed by the law. The Company can use this data to verify user identity in line with engagement initiated by the user. We will communicate with you using the contact information provided by you in order to respond to any queries that you may have and to provide any information that you may request regarding the Services. We may communicate with you either by written, physical communication, email, telephone, SMS or via notifications on your mobile device. We may also send strictly service-related announcements to you periodically and when it is necessary to do so. For instance, if our services are temporarily suspended for maintenance, we might send you an email, text message, flash notification or telephone call. If you do not wish to receive such alerts, you have the option to unsubscribe from such emails or opt out by sending an email to [legal@gminsights.com](mailto:legal@gminsights.com).  

**We may use Personal Information or Usage Information collected through the Website in the following ways:**

·              To operate and improve our Website and tools associated with the Website;

·              To create aggregated and anonymized information to determine which Website features are most popular and useful to users, and for other statistical analyses;

·              To prevent, discover and investigate violations of this Privacy Policy or the Terms and Conditions, and to investigate fraud or other matters;

·              To customize the content or the Services on the Website for you, or the communications sent to you through the Website.

·              To help provide you the Services;

·              To observe, improve and administer the quality of Service;

·              To analyze how the Website is used, diagnose technical problems;

·              Remember the basic information provided by you for effective access;

·              To confirm your identity in order to determine your eligibility to use the Website and avail the Services;

·              To notify you about any changes to the Website;

·              To enable the Company to comply with its legal and regulatory obligations;

·              For the purpose of sending administrative notices, Service related alerts and other similar communication with a view to optimizing the efficiency of the Website;

·              Doing market research, troubleshooting, protection against error, project planning, fraud and other criminal activity; and

·              To reinforce the Company’s Terms of Use.  

3.2.         **_Anonymous_** :

We may share non-Personal Information, such as aggregated user statistics and log data, with our business partners for industry analysis, demographic profiling, to deliver targeted advertising about other products or services, or for other business purposes. This information is solely used to analyze company website and understand usage statistics, as mentioned above, is anonymous. The company may share this data with its business partners on anonymous basis.  We do not sell, share, rent or trade the information we have collected about you, including Personal Information, other than as disclosed within this Privacy Policy or at the time you provide your information. We do not share your Personal Information with third parties for those third parties’ direct marketing purposes unless you consent to such sharing at the time you provide your Personal Information.  

3.3.         **_When You Agree To Receive Information from Third Parties:_**

You may be presented with an opportunity to receive information and/or marketing offers directly from third parties with whom you have created a transaction through the Website. If you do agree to have your Personal Information shared, your Personal Information will be disclosed to such third parties and all information you disclose will be subject to the privacy policy and practices of such third parties. We are not responsible for the privacy policies and practices of such third parties and, therefore, you should review the privacy policies and practices of such third parties prior to agreeing to receive such information from them. If you later decide that you no longer want to receive communication from a third party, you will need to contact that third party directly.  

3.4.         **_Administrative and Legal Reasons_** _:_

 We cooperate with government and law enforcement officials and private parties to enforce and comply with the law. Thus, we may access, use, store, transfer and disclose your information (including Personal Information), including disclosure to third parties such as government or law enforcement officials or private parties as we reasonably determine is necessary and appropriate: (i) to satisfy any applicable law, regulation, governmental requests or legal process; (ii) to protect the safety, rights, property or security of the Company, our Services, the Website or any third party; (iii) to protect the safety of the public for any reason; (iv) to detect, prevent or otherwise address fraud, security or technical issues; and /or (v) to prevent or stop any activity we consider to be, or to pose a risk of being, an illegal, unethical, or legally actionable activity. Such disclosures may be carried out without notice to you.  

3.5.         **_Business Transfer:_**

We may share your information, including your Personal Information and Usage Information with our parent, subsidiaries and affiliates for internal reasons. We also reserve the right to disclose and transfer all such information: (i) to a subsequent owner, co-owner or operator of the Website or applicable database; or (ii) in connection with a corporate merger, consolidation, restructuring, the sale of substantially all of our membership interests and/or assets or other corporate change, including, during the course of any due diligence process. You will be notified via email and/or a prominent notice on our Website of any change in ownership or uses of your personal information, as well as any choices you may have regarding your personal information. We will endeavor that the transferee who is the recipient of Personal Information and Usage Information commits to privacy measures which are substantially similar to the measures under this privacy policy.  

3.6.         **_Consulting:_**

The Company may partner with another party to provide specific services if required. When you sign-up for the Services, the Company will share names, or other personal information that is necessary for the third party to provide these Services. The Company’s contractual arrangements with such third parties, restrict these parties from using personally identifiable information except for the explicit purpose of assisting in the provision of these Services. The Company also protects your personal information off-line other than as specifically mentioned in this Privacy Policy. Access to your personal information is limited to employees, agents or partners and third parties, who the Company reasonably believes will need that information to enable the Company to provide Services to you. However, the Company is not responsible for the confidentiality, security or distribution of your own personal information by our partners and third parties outside the scope of our agreement with such partners and third parties.

**4.             _THIRD PARTY CONTENT AND LINKS TO THIRD PARTY SERVICES_**

The Website may contain content that is supplied by or referred from a third party, and those third parties may collect website usage information and any other information when web pages from any online or mobile services are provided to your browser. In addition, when you are using the Website, you may be directed to other sites or Websites that are operated and controlled by third parties that we do not control. We are not responsible for the privacy practices employed by any of these third parties. These other websites may send their own cookies to you, independently collect data or solicit personal information and may or may not have their own published privacy policies. When you leave our Website, we encourage you to read the privacy statements of all third party websites or Websites before submitting any information to third parties.

**5.             _DATA TRANSFER_**

Your information collected through the Website may be stored and processed in United States of America or any other country in which the Company or its subsidiaries, affiliates or service providers maintain facilities. The Company may transfer information that we collect about you, including Personal Information, to affiliated entities, or to other third parties across borders and from your country or jurisdiction to other countries or jurisdictions around the world. These countries may have data protection laws that are different to the laws of your country and, in some cases, may not be as protective. We have taken appropriate safeguards to require that your information will remain protected in accordance with this Privacy Policy.

**6.             _DATA RETENTION_**

Your information will be retained with the Company as long as it is needed by the Company to provide Services to you. If you wish to cancel your account or request that the Company no longer uses your information to provide Services, you may contact the Company at [legal@gminsights.com](mailto:legal@gminsights.com). The Company will promptly delete the information as requested. The Company will retain and use your information as necessary to comply with its legal obligations, resolve disputes, and enforce its agreements or for other business purposes. When the Company has no ongoing legitimate business need to process your information, we will either delete or anonymize it.

**7.             _SECURITY_**

This website, in compliance with PCI – DSS norms, has a number of security measures to ensure there is no loss, misuse or illegal alteration of information collected from its users. Personal Information and Usage Information we collect is securely stored within our databases, and we use standard, industry-wide, commercially reasonable security practices such as encryption, firewalls and SSL (Secure Socket Layers) for protecting your information. However, as effective as encryption technology is, no security system is impenetrable. We cannot guarantee the security of our databases, nor can we guarantee that information you supply won't be intercepted while being transmitted to us over the Internet or wireless communication and any information you transmit to the Company you do at your own risk. If, despite our best efforts, an unauthorised breach of our security measures occurs, resulting in the unauthorised access, duplication, removal or alteration of any Personal Information, Third Party Information, or Usage Information, the Company, its directors, officers, employees, promoters, or affiliates will not be held responsible for any loss resulting from such breach.

**8.             _COMPROMISE OF PERSONAL INFORMATION_**

In the event that personal information is compromised as a breach of security, the Company will promptly notify our customers in compliance with applicable law.

**9.             _CONTACT & POLICY UPDATES_**

In case on any queries on this privacy policy, please contact us at [legal@gminsights.com](mailto:legal@gminsights.com). The Company reserves the right to update or modify any part of this policy or make any changes without prior notice to the user. The user is advised to check this page periodically to stay abreast of any policy changes by us

**10.           _CHILDREN’S PRIVACY_**

Protecting the privacy of young children is especially important. For that reason, the Company does not knowingly collect or solicit personal information from anyone under the age of 13. In the event that we learn that we have collected personal information from a child under age 13, we will delete that information as quickly as possible. If you believe that we might have any information from or about a child under 13, please contact us at [legal@gminsights.com](mailto:legal@gminsights.com).

**11.           _CHANGE OF INFORMATION AND CANCELLATION OF ACCOUNT_**

You are responsible for maintaining the accuracy of the information you submit to us, such as your contact information provided as part of account registration. If your Personal Information changes, or if you no longer desire to access the Website, you may correct, delete inaccuracies, or amend information by making the change on our member information page or by contacting us through [legal@gminsights.com](mailto:legal@gminsights.com) and we will respond within 48 to 72 business hours of receipt of communication. You have the right to request that we rectify or delete the personal data or restrict the processing of your personal data, if you think they are inaccurate. Furthermore, you have the right to object against the processing based on our legitimate interests as a legal basis. We are required to assess and act on your request. Additionally, you also have the right to data portability if it should become relevant. You have a right to lodge a complaint with your local supervisory authority.

You may also cancel or modify your communications that you have elected to receive from the Website by logging into your user account and changing your communication preferences.

If you wish to cancel your account or request that we no longer use your information to provide you details with respect to our Services and the Website, please write to us at [legal@gminsights.com](mailto:legal@gminsights.com).

**12.           _OPT IN_**

If you wish to opt for receiving non-essential communications such as promotional and marketing-related information regarding the Website and the Services, please send the Company an email at [legal@gminsights.com](mailto:legal@gminsights.com) .

**13.           _CHANGES TO THE PRIVACY POLICY_**

From time to time, we may update this Privacy Policy to reflect changes to our information practices. Any changes will be effective immediately upon the posting of the revised Privacy Policy on the Website. If we make any material changes, we will notify you by email (sent to the e-mail address specified in your account) or by means of a notice on the Website prior to the change becoming effective. We encourage you to periodically review this page for the latest information on our privacy practices.

**14.           _GRIEVANCE REDRESSAL_**

If you have any questions or concerns about this Privacy Policy, please feel free to contact us by writing to us at [legal@gminsights.com](mailto:legal@gminsights.com) or using the details provided on our ‘Contact Us’ page. We will use reasonable efforts to respond promptly to requests, questions or concerns you may have regarding our use of personal information about you. Except where required by law, the Company cannot ensure a response to questions or comments regarding topics unrelated to this policy or Company’s privacy practices.

**15.           _CONSENT:_**

By consenting to the terms under this Privacy Policy, you are expressly granting the Company the right to collect, share, transfer, store, retain, disseminate or use the Personal Information/Usage Information collected by the Company from your usage of the Website in accordance with the terms of the Privacy Policy. You may, at any time, withdraw consent for the collection or processing of Personal Information/Usage Information by sending an email to [legal@gminsights.com](mailto:legal@gminsights.com). The Company, shall within 48 to 72 business hours delete or anonymize the data collected from you.
